Auburn (NY) Area Labor Council Records 5892
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Auburn (NY) Area Labor Council Records
1929-1986
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Auburn (NY) Area Labor Council
5892
1.89 cubic feet
1.8 linear ft.
Records (documents).
5725210
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 28, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Auburn (N.Y.) Area Labor Council is part the New York State AFL-CIO which is a federation of 3,000 affiliated public sector, private sector, and building trades unions throughout the state, representing 2.5 million members, retirees and their families
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5892 AV: Auburn (NY) Area Labor Council Audio-Visual Materials 5892 MB: Auburn (NY) Area Labor Council Memorabilia 5892 mf: Auburn (NY) Area Labor Council "Meeting Minutes of the Auburn (NY) Area Labor Council" and Amalgamated Meat Cutters, Butcher Workmen and Affiliated Crafts of North America on Microfilm
Municipal officials and employees -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- Auburn; Transport workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- Auburn; Insurance companies -- Employees -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- Auburn; Construction workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- Auburn; Auburn (N.Y.). Area Labor Council
5725210
- Auburn Area Labor Council Miscellaneous Papers, 1957-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Auburn Newspaper Clippings pertaining to AFL-CIO, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Auburn Labor Council Correspondence, 1958-1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Auburn Labor Council Meeting Minutes, 1961-1986 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Auburn Labor Council Subject File, 1960-1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Auburn Labor Council Publications and Documents, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Minutes of the Auburn Labor Council, 1950-1953 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound book, handwritten
- AFL-CIO Union Label Cartoons (Box 2)
- AFL Union Label Dept., Certificates, Charters, Union Label poster - Auburn, NY (Box 3)
  - AFL Union Label Dept., Certificates, Charters, Union Label poster - Auburn, NY; 1 oversize photo of Bro. of Painters, sorted from box of 'misc. photos' that was housed over mapcase (Box 3, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Union Label Cartoons (Box 4)
- Auburn Federation of Labor; Meat cutters Local No.2; Officers C.I.O. - (photos) - s1904; [rolled photo] - 93rd Convention of the NY State Federation of Labor - June 25-28, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  items removed from box 1
- Auburn, NY Area Labor Council (Box 4, Folder 2)
  removed from Bx 3/Map case 9